GBENGA ADEKOYA

Address: 1, Lane C, Abese Zone 7, Oluyole Extension, Ibadan, Oyo State

Mobile: +234 813 697 8691 & +234 901 890 3008

E- mail:adekoyagbenga24@gmail.com

Objective

A motivated, adaptable, proactive and responsible individual, ready to utilize the professional and technical skills developed through past work experience for the betterment of the organization. I have a customer-focused approach to work and a strong drive to see things through to completion.

Education

2005 – 2010 BSc (Ed.) Educational Management/Economics (Hons) University of Ado-Ekiti

2nd Class Degree with Upper Division (4.28) CGPA

Relevant Modules:

- Professional and Social Aspect of Educational Management Information System (EMIS)(70%)
- Data Collection, Data Processing, Data Analysis and Data Reporting System (67%)
- Understanding Economics of Educational Management Information System(EMIS) (93%)
- Student Information System (71%)
- Managing Human and Financial Recourses

•

1998 – 2014 West Africa Secondary Certificate Examination Alpha Plus High School

• 7 WASSCE at grade A-C

Work Experience

2018 - 2019

On-Air Personality

TSOLID MEDIA

- Created and provided compelling content on the air
- Made regular approved appearances of station events
- Maintained a positive and approachable attitude when around listeners and clients
- Prepared and delivered news, sports reports, gathering and rewriting materials so that it will convey required information and fit specific time slots
- Portrayed a strong work ethic; punctuality with a cooperative attitude.

- Limited
 - Developed viable marketing strategies
 - Managed principal agencies
 - Ensured timely delivery of operational tools
 - Administered existing and potential principal and sub-agents' field attitudes and performances
 - Team-led the entire marketing crew on diverse marketing techniques, trainings and platforms
 - Trained and mentored new and existing marketing staff members
 - Other assigned function given from time to time

2014 Sales Personnel AIICO Insurance

- Attended meetings, seminars and programs
- Attracted new clients and developed clientele by networking to find new customers and generate lists of prospective clients.
- Sold various insurance policies to cooperate entities and individual, including automobile, fire, life property, medical and dental insurance or specialized policies such as marine, farm/crop.
- Explained features, advantages and disadvantages of various policies to promote sale of insurance policies and plans
- Ensured proper filing of policy requirement, including and necessary medical examinations and completion of appropriate forms.
- Developed marketing strategies to complete with other individual or companies who sell insurance policies

2013 High School Teacher Pacey Manuel College

- Taught government and civic education
- Prepared lesson notes
- Coordinated continuous assessments and examinations
- Marked scripts and collated results
- Planned and coordinated maiden inter house sports

2011- 2012 National Youth Service Corps (NYSC) Community Secondary School

· Taught economics and commerce

- Prepared lesson note
- Coordinated continuous assessments and examinations
- Marked scripts and collated results
- Advanced community development via project and teamwork

Computer Skills

• WINDOS/DOS: MS Word, Excel, MS Access and MS Power point

Hobbies and Interests

Reading (motivational and historical books), Music, Sports, Travel.

Language(s)

English, Yoruba, French (in-view)

Referees

All shall be gladly available on request